flickchart.com 2017-11-21

# Privacy Policy - Flickchart

### Stuff About You

We may collect any of the following information during your time at Flickchart:

  * your name

  * contact information including your email address

  * and demographic information such as your zip code, preferences and interests

That's it. If we ever need or want more information from you than that, we'll be sure to tell you exactly when and why. No mysteries here.

### What we do with the Stuff About You

  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new features, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address you signed up with.

  * We may also use the information to customize Flickchart according to your particular interests.

### Cookies! Yum!

A cookie is a small file which lives on your computer's hard drive. The cookie helps us to adjust Flickchart to your unique needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We also use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve Flickchart.. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may, however, prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Our Advertisers

Our advertising providers may engage in the collection of **_non-personally identifiable_** information about you (the user) by third parties through the use of cookies and pixel tags. While this collection is intended to provide you with more personally relevant advertising, you may at any time [opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) of behavioral targeting. Flickchart, by way of its advertisers, is also a participant in the Digital Advertising Alliance's (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising, which you may choose to [opt-out](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) of as well.

### We won't sell you out

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. Pretty simple. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

### Changes to This Policy

As we update and expand our services, we may make changes to this policy. You should check back for updates to this policy from time to time. If the changes result in materially less protection for your personal information than that provided in this policy, we will make reasonable efforts to contact you and obtain your consent to the changes. Like our Terms of Service, of which this policy is a part, your continued use of Flickchart after our efforts to contact you means that you agree to be bound by such changes.

Thanks for reading! Have fun here at Flickchart!

_Last updated May 5th, 2012._
